bodyartforms.com 2019-03-07

# Privacy policy

Bodyartforms Privacy Policy 

Last modified May 20th, 2018  
Effective May 21st, 2018

#### WELCOME TO BODYARTFORMS!

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from Bodyartforms.com.

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to www.bodyartforms.com and Bodyartforms, LLC and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Bodyartforms, LLC include www.bodyartforms.com and Bodyartforms. The Bodyartforms website is an ecommerce site. By using the Bodyartforms website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Bodyartforms does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

#### Collection of your Personal Information

In order to better provide you with products and services offered on our Site, Bodyartforms may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:

  * First and Last Name
  * Shipping & Billing Addresses
  * E-mail Address
  * Phone Number

If you purchase Bodyartforms's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction and anything else related to the purchase order, like refunds etc. Billing and credit card information securely passes directly to Authorize.net. They are a leading provider of payment management services and are PCI compliant. If you choose to save credit card/billing information it is stored with them. Bodyartforms does not  store any credit card information. We can only view the last four numbers of credit cards after an order has been placed.

Here is a link to Authorize.net’s privacy policy:   
<https://www.authorize.net/company/privacy/>

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Bodyartforms's user submitted product reviews or photos, this information may be collected and used by others. We do not disclose your email publicly.

We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) sending us an email message; (c) submitting product reviews or photos; (d) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. We will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

#### Use of your Personal Information

Bodyartforms collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested. Bodyartforms may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Bodyartforms.

#### Sharing Information with Third Parties

Bodyartforms does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Bodyartforms may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you emails, provide customer support, upgrade website features & security, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Bodyartforms, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above.  For example we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here:  [https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/.](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.>

Bodyartforms may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Bodyartforms or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Bodyartforms; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Bodyartforms, or the public.

#### Use of Device Information

We use Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

For example we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here:  [https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/.](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)   

You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.>

#### Tracking User Behavior

Bodyartforms may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Bodyartforms, in order to determine what Bodyartforms services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Bodyartforms to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

#### Automatically Collected Information

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Bodyartforms. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Bodyartforms website.

#### Use of Cookies

The Bodyartforms website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Bodyartforms pages, or register with Bodyartforms site or services, a cookie helps Bodyartforms to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Bodyartforms website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Bodyartforms features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Bodyartforms services or websites you visit.

For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

#### Google reCAPTCHA

We use “Google reCAPTCHA v3” (hereinafter “reCAPTCHA”) on our websites. This service is provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA (“Google”).

reCAPTCHA is used to check whether the data entered on our website (such as on a contact form) has been entered by a human or by an automated program. To do this, reCAPTCHA analyzes the behavior of the website visitor based on various characteristics. This analysis starts automatically as soon as the website visitor enters the website. For the analysis, reCAPTCHA evaluates various information (e.g. IP address, how long the visitor has been on the website, or mouse movements made by the user). The data collected during the analysis will be forwarded to Google.

The reCAPTCHA analyses take place completely in the background. Website visitors are not advised that such an analysis is taking place.

Data processing is based on Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO. The website operator has a legitimate interest in protecting its site from abusive automated crawling and spam.

For more information about Google reCAPTCHA and Google’s privacy policy, please visit the following links: <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en> and <https://policies.google.com/terms?hl=en>.

#### Security of your Personal Information

Bodyartforms secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Bodyartforms uses the following methods for this purpose:

  * SSL Protocol

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed. 

#### YOUR DATA RIGHTS AND CHOICES

We believe that users should be treated equally no matter where they are, and so we are making the following options to control your data available to all users, regardless of their location.You can update certain information by accessing your profile via “Your Profile.” You can also unsubscribe from certain emails by clicking the “unsubscribe” link they contain. Individuals in the European Economic Area, Canada, Costa Rica and some other jurisdictions outside the United States have certain legal rights to obtain confirmation of whether we hold personal data about them, to access personal data we hold about them (including, in some cases, in portable form), and to obtain its correction, update, amendment or deletion in appropriate circumstances. 

How can I access the personal data you have about me?

If you would like to submit a data access request, you can do so from the “Contact Us” page located at the bottom left side of the website.

<http://www.bodyartforms.com/contact.asp>

How do I correct, update, amend, or delete the personal data you have about me?

In addition to the functionality available through “My Profile”, in which you can correct, update, amend, or delete certain personal data, you can also request other modifications from us directly. Please contact us through the “Contact Us” page with the words “Personal Data Request” in the subject or body of your message, along with an explanation of what data subject right you are seeking to exercise. For your protection, we may take steps to verify identity before responding to your request.

How do I object or restrict the manner in which Bodyartforms processes my personal data?

You have a right to ask us to stop using or limit our use of your personal data in certain circumstances. Individuals in the European Economic Area have the right to opt out of all of our processing of their personal data for direct marketing purposes. To exercise this right, please click the “unsubscribe” link in any of our marketing emails.The rights and options described above are subject to limitations and exceptions under applicable law. We encourage you to contact us, and we will do our very best to resolve any of your concerns.

#### Children Under Thirteen

Bodyartforms does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

#### E-mail Communications

From time to time, Bodyartforms may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication. In order to improve our Services, we may receive a notification when you open an email from Bodyartforms or click on a link therein.

If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from Bodyartforms, you may opt out of such communications by hitting the unsuscribe button in the email, or by contacting us at <http://www.bodyartforms.com/contact.asp>.

#### External Data Storage Sites

We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.

#### Changes to this Statement

Bodyartforms reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.

#### Contact Information

Bodyartforms welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Bodyartforms has not adhered to this Statement, please contact us at:

Bodyartforms, LLC  
1966 S Austin Ave  
Georgetown, Texas 78626 

Contact us via e-mail here:  
<http://www.bodyartforms.com/contact.asp>

Telephone number:  
877-223-5005
